[Negan]
Previously onDead City.
[The Croat] With the methane.
we can bring the city back.
[Negan] Right around the time
that the world turned into
shit soup.
The Croat showed up at my door.
Said that I made him feel safe.
[Dama]
He murdered your husband.
-[Negan grunts]
-[Maggie grunts]
Just look after Ginny. will ya?
No!
[Dama] Our world
has been destroyed.
So now. we get
to build something new.
[eerie music]
[hammer pounding]
[eerie music continues]
[Soldier] Hey. who are you?
You're not supposed to be here.
[referee whistle blows]
Do you hear that?
Maybe we should get in there.
No... Sarge told us to hang
these up all around. come on.
Lead the way.
You lead the way.
Always tellin' me what to do.
[gunshots]
[people shouting]
[tense music]
[wind whipping]
[tense music continues]
[shouting]
[walkers growling]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[gentle music]
[shovel thudding]
What the hell are you doing?
You were sleeping.
-[Negan scoffing]
-Armstrong and I got to talking.
She was myresponsibility.
Mine!
I was...
I was tryin' to do you a favor.
You're still
healing from the wound.
Where you stabbed me
in the goddamn back?
Never ends with you. does it?
Uh. first. you lure me
to this goddamn island.
and then you lie to me.
and then you hand me over
to some psychopath
because you think you're
gonna get your son back.
But you don't get your son back
because he sees the psychopath
as the mama you'll never be.
Don't.
[Negan] Doesn't end there.
though. does it?
No.
Why don't you try murdering me
as the cherry on top
of your shit sundae
of shit ideas
and pretend you don't torch
everything you touch
by burying the one person
-on this godforsaken island...
-Listen to me!
I am sorry.
I'm sorry for what I did.
I'm sorry for what you lost.
If I could undo anything
that's been done. I would.
Would you?
This... This is where we are.
And we can either keep rehashing
all this shit
that we can't change.
or we can try to move on.
I have nothin' to move on to
thanks to you.
[somber music]
I'm stayin' put for Hershel.
You got nothin'
and no one to stay put for.
So why don't you go?
I'll help you pack your bags.
Who are you kiddin'?
You're never gonna let me go.
All I am to you.
all I ever will be...
is a big old shit pile
of the shittiest shit
that I have ever done.
The fact of the matter is.
you need someone as shitty as me
because I am
the only person shitty enough
to make you feel less shitty
about your shit pile of a life.
So do me a favor and go ahead
and keep twistin' that knife.
because we both know
that is the one goddamn thing
that you'll do
without screwin' up.
Okay. then you fucking stab me.
Take it. Clean slate. Let's go.
-[Maggie] Here.
-[chuckling]
I don't wanna die. okay?
But I will gladly bleed a little
if it'll make you shut
that gapin' bullshit hole.
So either do it or for the love
of God. shut the fuck up.
It is a one-time offer
with a ten-second
expiration date.
so you better get to it... Ten.
-Nine. eight. seven. six...
-You are batshit.
Probably... Five. four...
-Three...
-I'm gonna do it.
-Do it! Two. one...
-[Renata] Drop your weapons!
[dramatic music]
She said drop your weapons!
-You got bullets in those guns?
-You wanna find out?
And whatever the hell that is.
What is this. all right?
What do you want?
We were on our way
to the cathedral
to steal a methane tank.
Heard you call him Negan.
Rumor has it that's the name
of the Croat's #2.
[Luis]
With your boy here as leverage?
Our plan just got a hell
of a lot easier.
My boy?
He just had a knife on me.
I've got nothin'
to do with this.
Oh. she's lyin'.
She is definitely the Croat's
#3.
Listen to me. You...
Both of you. shut up!
-[Negan chuckling]
-[Renata] Go!
You are makin' a mistake.
The Croat is in the wind.
It's New Babylon who's got
control
of those methane tanks now.
So if you want us to get close.
any of us. we get hanged:
you. us. all of us.
Bullshit. Get walking
-Go.
-Come on. Come on.
[tense music]
-[Luis] Alley on your right.
-[Renata] Clear.
[tense music continues]
Is he your brother?
I see the resemblance.
Yeah. He yours?
No. Definitely no.
Well. you sure
as hell fight like it.
[Luis]
Cellar door on your left.
[Renata] Looks clear.
[Hershel] Mom? Mom?!
-Hershel?
-Mom!
[explosions rumbling]
[dramatic music]
[fire crackling]
[shouting. screaming]
[tense music]
[walkers groaning]
-[Luis and Renata grunting]
-[walkers groaning]
[Renata] All the dead
in this city are going
to be coming this way
after that explosion.
We need to find cover.
We need to find Negan.
[walker snarling]
[thudding]
-[Negan grunting]
-[walker groaning and snarling]
-[walkers groaning and snarling]
[Maggie] Hershel!
Hershel. where are you?
-Hershel. down here!
-[Hershel panting]
[Maggie] Hershel!
Can you hear me?!
Mom?
-[Hershel coughing]
-[walkers growling]
Hershel!
[walker snarling]
-[grunting]
-[walker growling]
I'm sorry for this.
-[Negan] For what?
-[Maggie grunting]
-[Negan groaning]
-[Maggie] That.
God. I so should've stabbed you.
[dramatic music]
[walkers snarling]
-[Negan groaning]
-[walkers growling and snarling]
-[The Croat panting]
[grunting]
Luis! [sighs] Luis.
you look terrible. my friend.
You're gonna lead us
to the tanks.
You're gonna give us one.
and then you're going to die.
[walkers snarling]
[grunts]
The tanks?
What do you think that explosion
was?
Tanks are gone.
-What?
-[The Croat] What I created?
Falling into the hands of
those... New Babylon Visigoths?
No. They had to be exploded.
Then you'll make us one.
There won't be
time enough for that.
[dramatic music continues]
[The Croat breathes heavily]
-[Negan groaning]
-[walkers snarling]
[dramatic music continues]
[The Croat breathing heavily]
No. Luis! No. no.
[speaks Spanish] Come on.
It's not worth it. Luis...
[dramatic music continues]
-[Negan groaning]
-[walkers snarling]
[rattling and thudding]
-[Negan groaning and panting]
-[walker snarling]
[sighs wearily]
-[Maggie grunting]
[thudding. splat]
[walker grunts]
[dramatic music continues]
[walker snarling]
All right. dickhead.
I guess you get the honor.
[suspenseful music]
[walker snarling]
-Mom!? Are you down here?
-Over here!
-[walker snarling]
-[Maggie grunting]
Hershel...
[tense music]
-Where's your wrists?
-[Maggie panting] Oh God.
[dramatic music]
[walkers snarling]
Luis. it is not safe out here.
We need cover.
There!
[dramatic music continues]
[walkers growling]
What are you doin'?
Renata...
Damn it. leave him!
[dramatic music continues]
Shit!
[Renata coughing]
[Negan grunting]
[dramatic music continues]
Negan!
I had a feeling our paths would
cross again before the end.
You.
[suspenseful music]
No. no!
Stop. stop. stop. stop! Please.
We weren't gonna hurt you.
We were just tryin'
to keep a baby alive.
[dramatic music]
[upbeat Latin music]
[cork popping]
[cheering]
[upbeat Latin music continues]
[indistinct chattering]
[Renata] Yvette. the kids wanna
show you the stuffy they made
for the baby.
[Yvette. beyond touched]
Aww. It better not make me cry.
-Aw. see. Tio Chucho loves it.
-[giggling]
As if the world
weren't fucked up enough.
now there's gonna be a little
Chucho runnin' around here?
Can't believe it. dude.
I love you. bro.
[Luis] I love you. man.
[upbeat Latin music continues]
[music stops]
No. no. no. no.
Don't stop on my account.
You have much to celebrate.
My eyes and ears tell me
your family is expanding. yes?
Yes.
Yvette and Chucho
are having a baby.
[The Croat] Well. then.
I suppose congratulations
are in order.
Flowers from the cemetery.
And the world begins anew. eh?
[tense music]
And yet. Renata...
all this at the very time I have
an issue to address with you.
We have an arrangement. yes?
We protect you.
With respect.
the deal was forced on us.
We didn't need it.
So why don't we just end it?
The Burazi protect this island.
The deal ends when you leave it.
Are you leaving?
[Ramon] Our family's been here
a hell of a lot longer
than you guys have.
Well. good for you.
But the arrangement stands.
And the Dama's vision
of the future?
Well. it only succeeds if
everyone contributes something
valuable in return.
And as much as I want to
believe you can... I don't.
I was training some of
the others
in emergency medicine.
Okay... Doctors!
Doctors are a resource!
Your brother Chucho!
[laughs]
Is he among your trainees?
He is.
Well. Doctor Chucho.
let me take a look at you.
Come. come. come.
[tense music]
[The Croat] So...
Are you a resource. Doctor?
[tense music continues]
Yes.
Well. then prove it.
[knife thudding]
[gasping. exclaiming]
-No. no. no.
-[indistinct clamoring]
I've given you a patient.
Doctor.
Save him.
Don't leave me. tio.
Don't leave me!
-Stay with me. Stay with me.
-[Ramon groaning]
You know... I fear he is not
too good at this.
Maybe you are a bad teacher?
Or maybe you are lying to me
about this whole business?
[Chucho] Don't leave me. tio.
[speaking Spanish]
Just look at me. tio. No!
[The Croat] Huh...
[panting]
I have no choice.
-You just don't make the cut.
-No!
[group screaming. crying]
[gurgles]
[sobs hysterically]
Yvette...
[speaks Spanish]
You know.
Iwas someone's trainee once.
Hopefully better than Chucho.
And one of the many things
my mentor taught me was
that killing the right person
at the right time makes
everyone else fall in line.
So. I wonder...
Did I pick the right person...
persons?
Maybe we should
try this again. huh?
Who shall be the next patient.
huh?
Huh?
Eenie. meenie. miney...
Renata... Oh. Renata...
Do you really believe one
of those slapdash weapons
can save your family?
Everybody back.
[speaks Spanish]
[gas hissing]
I'm willing to die for them.
Are you?
I don't think you would.
You don't know me very well.
[gas hissing]
This isn't over. For any of you.
Again... Congratulations.
[gas hissing]
[tense music]
No. Chucho! No. Chucho!
Chucho. please?
[sobbing]
[somber music]
[walkers snarling]
[Hershel] They're closed.
but there's no lock.
My sister-in-law is
having her baby.
We need to go now.
All right. well.
walkers are swarming out there.
There's nothing any of us can
do about that.
[walkers groaning faintly]
[Maggie] Nobody is going
anywhere.
[walkers groaning faintly]
He and I are gonna make sure
that this place is safe.
If you would just let us
explain.
The baby is coming
two months early...
-Nobody...
-[Renata] If we don't...
kill anybody until we get back.
[dramatic music]
[walkers groaning faintly]
There's another door
up the stairs.
There may be a way out.
but it's secure.
Okay.
-How did you...
-I know Ginny's dead.
You know?
I saw you bury her.
And I went looking for you.
and...
Just wanted to see if
you were really gonna stay.
You thought that I wouldn't?
I wouldn't blame
you if you didn't.
When I got back. the Dama...
She knew what I did.
She started talkin' about how it
wasn't enough for me
to hurt you.
She told me I had to...
She told me I had to killyou.
Just like how I told you
to kill him.
I... I think it came from her.
Just being around her.
And I just didn't see it.
And I should've.
[Maggie]
No. It's what she does. Hershel.
She sees what people
are looking for. what they need.
and she uses it
to get what she wants.
It's easier than you would
think to lose yourself.
And you were right to be mad.
Because I wasn't there.
Yeah. after she told me to...
I started thinkin' about
the times you werethere.
the scary things
you made go away.
You made it so I had a life.
I don't want to spend it being
mad anymore. at you. at anyone.
Me neither.
[gentle music]
[Maggie] She's not gonna hurt us
anymore.
I won't let her.
We won't let her.
Soon as it's safe.
we're gonna get out of here.
go home. and start over.
Hershel.
you're gonna move mountains.
[angry shouting]
[yelling in Spanish]
[The Croat] You said Yvette is
only 7 months pregnant!
Luis. how can I help you
with your hand on my throat?
-[Maggie] Hey. hey!
-[angry shouting]
Were you gonna do anything
to try to stop this?
No. I'm puttin' the little ball
in the little cup.
[The Croat breathing heavily]
[Luis] This sociopath killed our
brother right in front of us
and our uncle.
[The Croat] Okay. maybe...
Maybe I handled things badly.
But I was just trying
to make a point.
-As my mentor taught me.
-[Renata] Mentor?
You said you would help.
They know the baby needs
an incubator to have any chance.
And a tank would make it run.
You need to show us how
to build one now.
There's no need to build.
There's still a tank left.
There is a single prototype
I hid away a long time ago
with plans and detail how
to make more.
Where? Where is it?
Oh and I tell you and he kills
me? No.
My story does not end
in a musty basement.
No. I'll show you.
It's not far from here.
So we go now.
He shows us where the tank is.
Our family's still waiting at
the hospital with the generator.
I told you. you're not gonna
last five minutes out there.
We don't know how long
he'll last in here.
Luis. she's right.
We are no good to anyone dead.
okay?
We wait it out here as long
as we can and thenwe go.
Listen to her. Luis.
Because what I'm offering
has value far beyond
the child's life.
It's my legacy.
Imagine your homes
with steady power.
your own fields to plow.
fauna to hunt.
all surrounded by water.
This island...
It could be your fortress...
Forever.
We just wanna save this baby.
And we will. [speaks Spanish]
When it's safe.
we could use some good fighters
to help us out there.
[gentle music]
[cup popping]
You can save this baby.
Haven't you learned by now what
happens to people stupid enough
to have hope in this world?
Look. I'm sorry.
You can try whatever
you want here.
but that baby
doesn't have a chance.
Oh. wow.
You're a real fighter.
[cup and ball clank]
You're right.
[tense music]
Where are you goin'?
We're in a bar. right?
I'm gonna go find a drink.
[walkers growling faintly]
[unsettling music]
[walkers growling]
[walker snarling]
-[walker snarling]
-[Dillard whistling]
[Dillard]
She's still being that way?
[walker snarling]
[Dillard] And what'd ya say to
her?
[Dillard] Well. have you thought
about... [groans like walker]?
That's classic Titicaca.
Don't you wish that... okay.
[laughs]
I hear you. buddy.
[floor creaking]
Hey there. amigo.
Quite the fustercluck out there.
amiright?
[chuckling]
You wanna pull up a stool?
Me and Cockenspiel's
about to start a game
of Fuck. Marry. Kill.
And Titicaca's bein'
a wet blanket.
so we could use a third.
And don't worry.
I made these guys nice and safe.
Name's Dillard. Skunky brewski?
Sure.
[Dillard] I thought pullin'
teeth would be hard.
but those nails were
a real son of a bitch.
-[walker growling]
-[Negan chuckling]
[Dillard] He likes you.
[chuckles]
Thank you.
Welcome to the bar.
[glass ringing]
Cheers.
[Dillard chuckling]
[walkers snarling]
Okay. That should hold.
You could've left
the Croat to die.
You didn't.
And because of you.
that baby still has a chance.
[walkers snarling faintly]
San Lazaro.
patron saint of hope and mercy.
It belonged to my dad.
He always told us
that we had a choice.
We could choose the fight
or we could choose the light.
[thudding]
[walkers snarling faintly]
[Hershel] So you can just
forgive the Croat
-after what he did?
-[Renata] No.
Never. Making him suffer...
I think about
that every single day.
[gentle music]
But once the killing starts.
when does it stop?
[gentle music continues]
You know. choosing
the light after that...
was the hardest
thing I've ever done.
It still is.
[gentle music continues]
But it's a choice
that I wanna keep making.
Me. too.
Just started.
Maybe when we're done here.
Luis can take a look
at Negan's back.
I put a knife
into it last night.
[Renata] Oh.
You. like. just just started.
[walkers snarling faintly]
[walker snarling]
Okay.
[snarling continues]
That is dastardly!
Fuck. that is fresh.
Cockenspiel.
[Negan chuckles]
He's gonna kill Audrey Hep.
marry Venus Williams.
And he says he's gonna bang
Barbara Bush like a screen door
in a twister.
I gotta ask.
Where are you from. man?
What planet do you come from?
Well. I'm actually from Earth.
I'm from here.
Upstairs studio apartment
actually.
from way before shit
went tits up.
So you have survived here
alone this whole time?
How?
[Dillard] So. over the years.
folks either cut bait or
croaked.
But I stayed.
And I stayed above dirt by
turnin' each floor into a link
in a CLVFC.
Closed Loop Vertical Food Chain.
okay?
It starts with the deadies
who go slipin'
'n slidin' into the basement.
Here we got those maggoes
maggin' on the deadie...
[upbeat music]
[flies buzzing]
Then you got the froggies
froggin' on the maggoes...
[upbeat music continues]
[frogs croaking]
Of course we got the turks
turkin' on the froggies...
Chain goes all
the way up to coyotes.
which are surprisingly delish.
by the way.
But I am happy to pump
the brakes on turkeys
if you're feelin' kinda peckish.
[lock rattling]
Did baloney used to be illegal?
Infection is spreading faster
than I'd hoped.
How can you tell?
Rising body temperature.
redness and swelling growing
outward from the wound.
And see this pus
and milky drainage right there?
Not good.
What can I do to help?
Use that water
to clean the wound.
I'll find something
to dress it with.
[Renata] So you think
with those plans you could bring
electricity to the Bricks?
We got someone there who used
to be a plumber tryin'
to figure it out.
My cousin Solmari's an engineer.
You should come back with us.
I mean. it's... It has been
hard there with the crops.
Really hard... But with power...
it could be a fresh start
for all of us.
And I need a fresh start.
[tense music]
So what kinda doctor are you?
Emergency medicine.
I'd been training my brother
before the Croat...
[somber music]
Had to brain my uncle after.
But when it came to Chucho.
I just... I couldn't.
You and your people.
you could come with me
and Hershel to The Bricks.
Thanks.
But this godforsaken city has
been our home for generations.
The Croat's right.
The city could
still be our home.
[gentle music]
[The Croat coughing]
[Luis] Hey. where's the tank?
Tell us where it is.
No. I'm coming with you.
End where I began.
It's not far...
[Luis]
He doesn't have much longer.
We need to go now.
[The Croat coughing]
I know it's not safe out there.
but we need your help.
We should help. At least try.
Okay.
[dramatic music]
[walkers snarling]
[Dillard] And if I had
spilled the beans on that one.
let's just say a whole boatload
of people would've had diarrhea.
-That is not appetizing.
-It's not.
Oh. shit.
Hello. Mason W. Dillard.
Welcome.
The Croat.
he doesn't have much time.
We have to go now.
What's the point?
I know that you think that
baby's dead. but that mother.
I know what she's been through.
I know what she's
going through right now.
We need numbers.
Please. We need you.
All right. well.
you need numbers.
why don't you ask my pal here.
Dillard?
I ain't goin' nowhere.
I need you.
[gentle music]
I finally got my son back.
and I need to know that
I'm not gonna lose him again.
I need to know
that things can work out.
They can't. Maggie.
Without you.
you're probably right.
I'm tired of bein' angry.
[gentle music continues]
Aren't you?
After it's done.
Luis can stitch you up
and you can be free of me.
free to do whatever you want.
I just... I need this
one last thing from you.
Please.
[gentle music continues]
God damn it.
I was just gettin'
all comfy and settled.
I really should've stabbed you.
You weren't gonna stab me.
Oh. I was sogonna stab
you a little bit.
[tense music]
[walkers growling]
-How much further?
-We're close.
-It's just ahead.
-Ahead where?
[Renata] He needs to tell us
where to go!
[Maggie] I got an idea.
Your mother. she sacrificed
everything for you.
-What would she say?
-[speaking Croatian]
Her legacy. your legacy.
is about to disappear forever.
-Come on.
-[speaking Croatian]
Does anybody speak Croatian?
[dramatic music]
Wait. I think I know where it
is. Keep goin'.
[dramatic music continues]
[walkers growling]
[Renata grunting]
[dramatic music continues]
[Negan] Okay. we're almost
there.
I think we're just gonna have
a seat. Maggie.
[dramatic music continues]
Okay.
Oh. sorry... I know.
[somber music]
I was so arrogant.
I tried to lead...
someone who only knows...
How to lead.
[somber music continues]
Hey...
[speaking Croatian]
[somber music continues]
[Negan crying]
[flag rattling]
[somber music continues]
[sniffling]
[dramatic music]
-Solmari. We got it.
-Oh. thank God!
Through those doors.
She's in the O.R.
Contractions are close.
-Take this.
-Can I help?
C'mon.
-[Renata] Evie!
-[Yvette moans]
Evie. we're here.
Mira. Solmari is setting up
the tank across the hall.
-[speaking Spanish]
-[laughing happily]
The baby's head is crowning.
Yvette. I'm gonna need you
to start pushing. okay?
I need blankets. water to boil.
and an extension cord for the
incubator.
[Renata] Okay!
[speaks Spanish]
[gentle music]
Okay.
[gentle music continues]
Come on. That's a good push.
-Another one just like that.
-Okay.
Push .Good. good. good.
-[Luis] C'mon.
-[gasping and panting]
Solmari?
When you're done over there.
I need you to come here
and help Hershel.
Why? Where are you going?
[dramatic music]
Tanks need methane.
[tense music]
[Chucho snarling]
[tense music continues]
[blade squelching]
[Luis breathing heavily]
[somber music]
[gentle music]
[machines beeping]
[no audible dialogue]
-[baby crying]
-[no audible dialogue]
[gentle music continues]
[upbeat Latin music]
[lively chatter]
Feels like I finally
got my brother back.
I'm so proud of him.
I'm sure he's proud of you.
You're just as responsible
as he is for things workin' out.
for what you chose.
[upbeat Latin music
continues faintly]
I was thinkin' when I go back
to the Bricks
and get things settled down...
maybe your people and my people.
we could be in business.
Maggie. you should bring
your people here.
Hey. everything the Croat said
about this place is true.
It is a fortress.
The only thing that we are
missing is someone who knows how
to keep things safe.
This isn't my home.
Why can't it be?
I'm serious. Maggie.
Give me one good reason why
this can't be your fresh start.
I mean. Maggie.
you and me together.
Just imagine.
I'll have to think about it.
I have to talk to Hershel.
Of course.
Nothing's more
important than family.
-[Negan groaning]
-[faint Latin music]
Are you really gonna
leave without sayin' goodbye?
Well. you know me.
Never one
to overstay my welcome.
Thank you.
For what you did today.
I wasn't sure
that I'd convince you.
Well. you did.
How?
I mean. you. um...
You said you needed me.
[Negan sighs]
You know what happened
this morning at Ginny's grave?
There was a lotta shit goin' on.
you know? But...
I wasn't mad at you
for tryin'to kill me.
I was mad at you
because you didn't.
[somber music]
[Negan sighing]
Why didn't you finish the job.
Maggie?
[somber music continues]
'Cause somewhere inside.
I knew you were capable
of what you did today.
You better be careful.
You're makin' my head
get all kinds of big.
[somber music continues]
[chuckling]
You know. I don't think
I've ever seen you smile.
It suits you.
[somber music continues]
[Negan groaning]
Well. you need me again...
-You know where I'll be.
-That bar? Really?
Turns out we might not
be goin' far.
Thinkin' about staying.
I think Hershel
really likes it here.
You really think
you can change it here?
Once we find the Dama.
who's left to stop us?
[somber music continues]
[dramatic music]
[tense music]
[walkers snarling]
[dumpster rumbling]
That's it...
-Oh. god... Oh. god.
-[groaning]
[walkers growling]
Shit!
[eerie music]
Oh. you poor boys.
You're hurt.
Half of Midtown... is gone.
-[Linus] There's no one left.
-No. There must be others.
You'll rest. you'll heal...
And when you're ready.
you'll help me find them.
And then we begin again.
Every empire starts
with the broken.
[eerie music continues]
Yes. our work is just beginning.
[suspenseful music]
This place is the start of
something else.
something better.
We could bring
in even more people.
Here we go.
The whole. you know.
New York City thing.
it is starting to feel
like home.
♪♪
You and Renata really got
something here. Maggie.
It's your job
to protect this place.
This is what we asked for
when we turned on that light.
♪♪
We've come to make a deal.
It gets in the wrong hands.
it could be dangerous.
If you were in charge.
none of this would be happening.
-What's going on?
-We're taking our home back.
I'm guessing this isn't
your first suicide mission.
Not hardly.
Look out!
♪♪
Together. we can do something
bigger than we've
ever done before.
♪♪
-You guys rolling?
-Yeah. I mean. I'm rolling.
-Yeah.
-[Laughs]
After this much time
we did a season...
-It shocked us.
-That shocked us.
Yeah.
You fucking stabbed me.
It is a one time offer with
a 10-second expiration date.
so you better get to it.
For the first couple
of years I was on the show.
Lauren can hardly look at me.
Her process as an actor. and...
I just didn't have
my glasses on.
Maybe didn't have
her glasses on.
[Both grunt]
Sorry. I thought you were
better on your feet.
Good to see you. too.
And then we started
this spin off.
Every scene.
it was always so heavy.
There was never a lightness
or a humor to it.
We are quite silly people
in a very dark world.
-And now it's...
-And now we...
-we can do it.
-We get to bring that
in front of the camera.
I'm going to flip
you around like this.
and you're gonna fucking
Bruce Lee the fuck out of them.
[Laughs]
I'm no help.
In this season.
they actually work together.
Heard you call him Negan.
Rumor has it that's the name
of the Croat's number two.
Maggy and Negan are zip tied
together. and there we go.
-Yeah. and you never see us...
-No.
Under other people's control.
They're at it with each other.
but this was
a great way of us being joined
in misery against another force.
-Yeah.
-Let's talk about this scene.
We need to find cover.
We need to find Negan.
One of the cellar doors
leading to the street is open.
Beneath the open door.
makeshift slide.
A beat later. Maggie.
Negan tumble down the slide.
-[Grunts]
The walkers immediately on them.
That was a cool sequence
that was sort of
still being worked out
closer to production.
-It got worked out on the day.
-That too.
[Both laugh]
You were being so nice.
[Laughter]
Originally it's a fight
in the streets. remember?
-And it was the dust.
-You had an eye infection.
-I had an eye infection.
-I had a nose.
-a sinus infection.
-Yeah. and we were...
So we couldn't do the
super dusty scene.
We were both like.
"We'll die. you know?"
-Yeah.
-My eye is going to fall
out of my head.
and she's just gonna die.
Yeah. and my nose
was going into my face.
I know we seem
like superheroes. but...
No. just kidding.
[Laughs]
I mean. I believe us for
what it's worth working together
that I'm here doing this.
and then Negan comes in.
I'm sorry for this.
-For what?
-[Walkers growling]
-[Grunts]
-[Walker crashing
And cut.
Good.
It's the first time we've
seen them really fight together
since season... yeah.
It could have been 11.
-We need numbers. please.
-We need you.
I need you.
I think what sets
the whole thing in motion.
of being able to move forward
is. for herself and for her son.
there has to be a life
without anger.
There has to be a moving
forward.
The possibilities
for this new world
and for us are tremendous.
I really should have
stabbed you.
You weren't gonna stab me.
Oh. I was so gonna
stab you a little bit.
♪♪
[outro music]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today